

# Illia M

### Contact

#### Additional Skills

- React.js, Redux, Next.js;
- Node.js, Express.js;
- JavaScript, ES6, TypeScript;
- HTML5, CSS3, SAAS, SCSS.
  - ReduxSaga, Redux Thunk;
  - Routing: React Router
  - Component Libraries:

MaterialUI, Ant Design, Bootstrap;

- Forms: React Forms, Formik;
- RESTful APIs and third-party APIs (Stripe, Facebook, Linkedin, Twitter, Youtube);
- PostgreSQL, MySQL, GraphQL, pure SQL queries;
- MongoDB, Cloud Functions, AWS;

Tools: Jira, Trello, Slack, Git (GitHub, Gitlab, Bitbucket);

Github:

https://github.com/Tender6795

## **Professional Summary**

I'm a full-stack web developer who's working with up-to-date and most effective technologies. I specialize in JavaScript-based frameworks and related libraries. To ensure the highest quality standards I adhere to best coding practices. Being an easy-going and friendly team player helped me successfully build great relationships with customers. I use uncommon approaches to problem-solving, thus focusing on making applications work efficiently under the hood.

# Work Experience

06/2021 - present

### Full-stack developer | SBS Team

- · solving issues and fixing bugs;
- creating new features and building projects from scratch;
- building microservices, APIs, back-end services, scaling and replication setup;
- working with Cloud Functions / AWS;
- optimizing and refactoring codebases of the existing services.

08/2018 - 06/2021

## Full-Stack Developer | devPuzzle

- creating UI with React;
- writing BE with Node.js/Express.js;
- good at building database architecture

PostgreSQL/MySQL/MongoDB;

- optimizing and refactoring code base of the existing services;
- · building APIs, back-end services.

#### Education

2016 - 2019

### IT-Academy "Step" | Zaporizhzhia

Master of Computer Applications (MCA)

2004 - 2008

#### **Zaporizhzhia College of Radio Electronics**

Master's degree

## Languages

English — Basic

Russian / — Native

Ukrainian